[{"id": 1472, "question": "Wal-Mart is not just the world's largest retailer . It's the world's largest company, which sells in three months what number-two retailer Home Depot sells in a year. Wal-Mart exercises its power for just one purpose: to bring the lowest possible prices to its customers. At Wal-Mart, that goal is never reached. The retailer has a clear policy for suppliers: On basic products that don't change, the price Wal-Mart will pay, and will charge shoppers, must drop year after year. But what almost no one outside the world of Wal-Mart and none of its 21,000 suppliers know is the high cost of those low prices. To survive in the face of its pricing demands, makers of everything from bikes to jeans have had to close US plants in favor of obtaining products from abroad. Indeed, the real story of Wal-Ma...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Still more quality goods will be provided.", "The food you get at Wal-Mart costs least.", "The value of Mal-Mart is over assessed.", "Wal-Mart is a very demanding company."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2026, "question": "Vancouver. B.C.--For six months. Ted Schredd and Deanna Kopel cycled around North America to show others a way to help the environment. \"Nobody wants to breathe dirty air--but for the air to change. People have to stop driving cars,\" says Ted, \"If more people start riding bikes, the air will be cleaner.\" Ted started his trip alone. He had $160 in his pocket and plans to cycle around North America. He left his hometown of Vancouver, and when he arrived in San Diego he got the chance to make some extra money for the rest of his 13, 000 km trip. A cyclist he met asked him to speak at an environment meeting in Texas. Within a few hours, Ted was on a plane to the meeting and a big surprise. When he met Deanna at the meeting, they talked for six hours straight. It was love at first sight. The ne...\n\nQ: Why did Ted speak at an environmental meeting?", "options": ["He could get a big surprise.", "He was in the city of the meeting.", "He hoped to find someone to help him.", "He wanted more people to know more about his opinion."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1188, "question": "Why do men die earlier than women? The latest research makes it known that the reason could be that men's hearts go into rapid decline when they reach middle age. The largest study of the effects of ageing on the heart has found that women's _ may be linked to the fact that their hearts do not lose their pumping power with age. \"We have found that the power of the male heart falls by 20-25 percent between 18 and 70 years of age,\" said the head of the study, David Goldspink of Liverpool John Moores University in the UK. \"Within the heart there are millions of cells that enable it to beat. Between the age of 20 and 70, one-third of those cells die and are not replaced in men,\" said Goldspink. \"This is part of the ageing process.\" What surprises scientists is that the female heart sees very l...\n\nQ: According to the text, the UK scientists have known that   _  .", "options": ["women have more cells than men when they are born", "women can replace the cells that enable the heart to beat", "the female heart loses few of the cells with age", "women never lose their pumping power with age"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2217, "question": "Davey wanted to play baseball. But fifty years ago, in his small town, he couldn't find enough players for two full teams or an empty lot big enough for a field. And when he played ball in his back yard, he just broke windows and got into trouble. So Davey began playing with a plastic golf ball and a broom handle for a bat. When his dad, David Mullaney, a former semi-pro baseball pitcher , realized his son was hurting his arm trying to throw curves with the little plastic ball, he decided to find a better solution. Mullaney got a bunch of hollow plastic _ from a local factory, sat down at his kitchen table and began cutting different size holes in the balls with a razor knife. He thought maybe the holes would alter the ball's flight and help his son throw curves and sliders without hurting...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that  _  .", "options": ["Mullaney made the invention of Wiffle ball with the help of his son", "fifty years ago people didn't like playing baseball very much", "Mullaney's attempts to help Davey better enjoy ball-playing led to the invention of Wiffle ball", "playing balls would hurt one's arm before the Wiffle ball's appearance"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2928, "question": "Kodak's decision to apply for bankruptcy protection is a sad, though not unexpected, turning point for a leading American corporation that pioneered consumer photography and dominated the film market for decades, but finally failed to adapt to the digital revolution. Although many attribute Kodak's downfall to \"complacency ,\" that explanation doesn't admit the efforts with which the company went to reinvent itself. Decades ago, Kodak invented the first digital camera in 1975 -- but in a fateful decision, the company chose to focus on its traditional film business. Large companies have a difficult time switching into new markets. For example, although Kodak predicted the rise of digital photography, its culture was too rooted in the successes of the past to fully welcome the future. In the ...\n\nQ: Why does the author mention Kodak's invention of the first digital camera?", "options": ["To show its effort to overcome complacency.", "To show its early attempt to reinvent itself.", "To show its quick adaptation to the digital revolution.", "To show its will to compete with Japan's Fuji photo."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 934, "question": "Talk about a real-life hero! Ten-year-old Larry Champagne from St. Louis, Missouri, hit the brake on a runaway school bus. He saved himself and 20 other kids on board from disaster. It all happened in one terrible accident. On the way to school, the bus driver, Ernestine Blackman, suddenly fell ill. Seeing the car was running away, the other kids started to scream, but Larry ran to the front and stopped the bus. \"At first I thought, 'We're going to die,'\" says Larry, \"but after I pressed the brake, I felt safe.\" Larry's speedy reaction made news all over the country. He appeared on TV shows as a hero. The bus company gave Larry a big gift. His school hung a medal of honor around his neck. \"My grandmother always tells me to do what's right,\" says Larry. He thanked his brother, Jerrick, 9, w...\n\nQ: Larry thanked his brother Jerrick for   _  .", "options": ["helping him get the bus driver up", "helping him work on his old truck", "teaching him how to find the brake", "teaching him how to stop the bus"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 851, "question": "Even if you are a good high-jumper, you can jump only about seven feet off the ground. You cannot jump any higher because the earth pulls you hard. The pull of the earth is called gravity. You can easily find out the pull of the earth. If you weigh yourself, you will know how much gravity is pulling you. Since there is gravity, water runs down hill. When you throw a ball into the air, it falls back down. Because of gravity, you do not fall off the earth as it whirls around. Then, can we get away from the earth and go far out into space? Now you can do it, because spaceships have been invented. Then spaceship will go so fast that it can escape the earth's gravity and carry you into space....\n\nQ: We can get away from the earth by spaceship because  _", "options": ["the spaceship goes very fast.", "the earth can't pull the spaceship.", "the spaceship has a strong force.", "the spaceship can jump higher than others."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 514, "question": "Job advertising on the web Register a new account Log in to an existing account Promote your casual work, graduate or internship ,opportunity with an advertisement on the Careers Centre database free of charge. Your advertisement will be viewable to all university of Sydney students and appear in 'Job Alert' - a daily email to subscribing students. You can also target alumni (up to five years after graduation) - advertise on our database and it will be visible at AlumniOnline. If you advertise through the Careers Centre you will need to agree to our advertising terms and conditions. Unpaid work We are unable to advertise unpaid internship work experience or volunteer positions unless: the position fulfills part of a University curriculum and has faculty approval, or it is a volunteer posit...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the article?", "options": ["Registering a new account every time you log in", "Advertisements are displayed for a minimum of two months.", "Advertising unpaid positions with registered non-profit organizations is permitted.", "All job ads will appear online once they are submitted."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3159, "question": "TheCastle of Monteriggioni Located in central Tuscany,the Castle of Monteriggioniwas built by the Republic of Siena at the beginning of the 13th century in orderto defend its southern border against Florence.With their impressive towers, they feature in Dante's Divine Comedy. MainSights Inside the town are the Church of Santa Maria Assunta,the battlements on the town walls and the small \"Monteriggioni in Arme\" museum, where there are models andlife-size armors . Every July within the wall of the town a special eventis celebrated: the Medieval Festival of Monteriggioni, one of the mostbeautiful festivals in the region. The city goes back in time to the MiddleAges, the streets are filled up with people in period costume creating a realatmosphere. Dances, live performances, music, theatre, ki...\n\nQ: The best way to travel around thesurrounding area is   _  .", "options": ["by car", "by bus", "by train", "on foot"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 774, "question": "Being able to experience a different environment and custom will give us a new perspective on everything we thought we knew and understood. Maybe, going abroad is an opportunity to look again at not only the country and the people who live there but also ourselves. I had never expected to visit Paris. The French culture didn' t interest me that much, and Paris seemed too big, too touristy, too much. But when I found myself standing next to the Opera National de Paris, completely alone and totally lost, I knew I was in for an interesting ride. I had decided to take a summer history class abroad, and Paris just happened to be where it was set. My teacher eventually found me and other jet-lagged students and walked us down to where we would be staying. Even then, tired, hungry, and feeling di...\n\nQ: The writer came to Paris because   _  .", "options": ["he wanted to have an interesting ride", "he attended a course in summer", "he admired its beautiful scenery", "he was alone and lost his way"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3197, "question": "Pingviman Hotel Offering an outdoor pool, Pingviman Hotel offers Thai-style rooms in Chiang Mai. Free WiFi is available through-out and a complimentary service takes guests to the Chiang Mai Night Bazaar. All rooms are equipped with a 48-inch flat-screen cable TV and DVD player. Facilities at this hotel include a business center, a fitness center and laundry services. There is also a tour desk and meeting facilities. We speak your language! Hotel Rooms:35 Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Situated in Chiang Mai's trendiest area, Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel Chiang Mai by Compass Hospitality boasts accommodation in a boutique hotel well-decorated with art works from the renowned local Thai artists. Free WiFi is offered all throughout the property. At Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel, guests will fin...\n\nQ: What can be infer from the passage?", "options": ["The bus of Pingviman Hotel can take guests to the Chiang Mai Night Bazaar.", "There are two hotels not far away from the Sunday Walking Street.", "Guests living in the De Chai Hotel can enjoy the beautiful city views.", "Art Mai Gallery Nimman Hotel sells artworks from local Thai artists."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3494, "question": "Do you know how to play a game called \"Musical Chairs\"?It is easy to play and most people enjoy it. All you need are some chairs, some people and some way of making music. You may use a piano or any other musical instrument, if someone can play it. You may use a tape recorder. You can even use a radio. Put the chairs in a row. The chairs may be put in twos, back to back. A better way is to have the chairs in one row with each chair facing in the opposite direction to the chair next to it. The game is easy. When the music starts, the players walk round the chairs. Everyone goes in the same direction, of course, they should walk in time to the music. If the music is fast they should walk quickly. If the music is slow, they should walk slowly. The person playing music cannot see the people in...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not suitable for playing musical chairs?   _  .", "options": ["A piano", "A radio", "A tape recorder", "A telephone"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3103, "question": "When I was 18, I had a motorbike accident that put me in a coma for three months. The doctors said there was little chance of my coming out of it, but my identical twin, Marcus, didn't believe them and carried on talking to me. My first words when I came to myself were, \"Hello, Marcus. \"Even though I had no memory of my own name, or that the woman crying at my bedside was my mother, I knew Marcus immediately; it was like a genetic memory. just felt close to him. As weeks went by, I still could remember nothing before the accident. Marcus was the only person I could relate to. I had to relearn everything, and Marcus helped me. Because of my twin I wasn't scared of having lost my memory; I believed everything he said. He became my memory, telling me about my school, friends, previous girlfri...\n\nQ: Which of the following words best describes Marcus?", "options": ["Dishonest.", "Thoughtful.", "Careful.", "Strict."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2109, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting. He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life. He is _ for news all the time, then after several years he may get a desk job, and life becomes a bit more settled. Let's look at his work a little more closely. In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match. Sometimes he may be so busy that he has hardly any time to sleep. And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty-handed. In the beginning, a reporter has to cover a very wide field. After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work. For example, he may finally be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports. Some reporters may...\n\nQ: Reporters who write on films are said to be lucky because they   _  .", "options": ["can see more film stars", "can see the films before most people see them in the cinema", "can pay less than other people", "can write anything they like"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2857, "question": "Sure, it's good to get along with your teacher because it makes that time you spend in the classroom more pleasant. And yes, it's good to get along with your teacher because, in general, it's smart to learn how to relate to the different types of people you'll meet throughout your life. But really, there's one super-important reason why you should get along with your teacher. Kids who get along with their teachers not only learn more, but they're more comfortable asking questions and getting extra help. This makes it easier to understand new material and do your best on tests. When you have this kind of relationship with a teacher, he or she can be someone to turn to with problems, such as problems with learning or school issues, such as bullying. As a kid in elementary or middle school, y...\n\nQ: The passage is most probably taken from  _  .", "options": ["children's literature", "an education magazine", "a science report", "an advertisement"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1252, "question": "Sons who have fond childhood memories of their fathers are more likely to be emotionally stable in the face of day-to-day stresses, according to psychologists who studied hundreds of adults of all ages. \"As our study shows, fathers do play a unique and important role in the mental health of their children much later in life,\" psychology professor Melanie Mallers of California State University said. For this study, 912 adult men and women between the ages of 25 and 74 completed short daily telephone interviews about that day's experiences over an eight-day period. The interviews focused on the participants' psychological and emotional distress (i.e.whether they were nervous, sad, etc.) and if they had experienced any stressful events that day. The participants were also required to answer q...\n\nQ: In the interviews, people were asked about all of the following things EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["their psychological distress", "their emotional distress", "their childhood stressful events", "their childhood relationships with their parents"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 15, "question": "A girl with blue eyes is a blue-eyed girl. A man with long legs is a long-legged man. A woman with white hair is a white-haired woman. Children who have good looks are good-looking children. What do you do when you want to buy clothes? You go to a shop. If you can find clothes that are the right size for you, and if they are ready to wear, you will probably buy them. They are called ready-made clothes. If you can not find clothes that are the right size, you will go to a tailor's shop. A tailor is a man who makes clothes. He will measure you carefully and will then make clothes for you. Such clothes are called tailor-made clothes. What do we call a man who is dressed badly? We call him a badly-dressed man. A woman who is dressed well is called a well-dressed woman. What do you wear when it...\n\nQ: 55. The clothes which you buy from the supermarket are called    _    clothes.", "options": ["tailor-made", "ready-made", "hand-made", "mass production"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3258, "question": "\"Ten years ago I could never have imagined I'd be doing this,\"says Greg Pal,33,a former software executive. \"I mean ,this is essentially agriculture ,right? But the people I talk to, especially the ones coming out of business school , think this is the one hot area everyone wants to get into .\" He means bugs. To be more accurate, the genetic change of bugs---very, very small ones---so that when they feed on agricultural waste such as woodchip or wheat straw ,they do something extraordinary . They excrete crude oil. Unbelievably ,this is not science fiction .Mr. Pal holds up a small cup of bug excretion that could ,in theory ,be poured into the tank of the big Lexus SUX next to us .Not that Mr. Pal was willing to risk it just yet .He gives it a month before the first vehicle is filled up wi...\n\nQ: Greg Pal used to  _  .", "options": ["have great interest in bugs", "major in agriculture", "be engaged in developing software", "study in a business school"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1200, "question": "It is under the CPC's leadership that China has overcome many challenges in its economic, political and social systems and achieved remarkable progress the world has ever seen. Under the CPC's leadership, China has become the world's largest second largest economy. People's lives have greatly improved, and hundreds of millions of people have been lifted out of poverty, an objective fact no one can deny. At the same time, China is quickly becoming a major player on the world stage. As a responsible nation, China has been playing a growing role and shouldered greater responsibilities in world affairs. Such achievements, especially for a nation with a size equaling to a continent and a population of nearly 1.4 billion, are not easy to make. What roles do you think CPC has played in China? Do ...\n\nQ: How does the author feel about the roles the CPC has played in China?", "options": ["Dissatisfied", "Amazed", "Annoyed", "Proud"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1214, "question": "A number of times Rosemary edged closer to Gordon , meaning to take his arm, but he edged away from her. She thought that she had offended him deeply, and that he was disappointed because she had pushed him away. She would have apologized if he had given her half a chance. But as a matter of fact, he was scarcely thinking of this any longer. It was the money business that was troubling him now. And the fact was that he would soon have to confess it. What nonsense it made of all he had said! Presently she stopped him, and swung him round to face her. \"Gordon, why won't you speak to me?\" she said. \"Are you still angry with me for what happened just now?\" \"No, I was never angry with you. You're not to blame. Something else has been worrying me all the way along, I've only eight pence left. I ...\n\nQ: Rosemary made him look at her because    _   .", "options": ["she wanted to ask him a question", "she wanted to see his face", "she was angry with him", "he had been rude"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 222, "question": "Bob was born in Cambridge. When he was in elementary school, he asked his mother to take him to parks in their community so he could collect empty soda cans to recycle. His mother agreed, as long as he saved part of the money he earned for college. Bob's mother remembers Bob as the most determined of her seven kids. Bob's persistence paid off. On Friday, he will become the first person in his family, originally from El Salvador, to graduate from college. And he's graduating with university honors. For his honors thesis he researched unmanned solar-powered airplanes, which BYU students have been building and testing for about 10 years. Bob's study helps discover the best way to fly a solar-powered airplane so that it uses the least amount of power. The goal is to design and build an airplan...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Bob  _  .", "options": ["researched unmanned solar-powered airplanes for 10 years", "paid for all his study by collecting empty soda cans", "worked hard and has graduated from college", "was affected by his family and has made some achievements"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2010, "question": "Are you addicted to computer games? Do you stay up all night playing them? Do you feel happy after you play computer games? There's no doubt that the excitement and appealing of games these days makes them hard to put down. We are attracted by the choice when it comes to gaming: You can role play--creating your own fantasy characters and stories, giving you a chance to step out of everyday life into an imaginary world. And there are shooting games where you can let out your anger and depression in violent situations where you kill people with guns. You can get excited from the games. However, can these kinds of games really be fun and can being absorbed in virtual reality be good for us? Should we worry about their effects on our health? Popular games like Grand Theft Auto have been blamed...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following shows the good influence on social lives?", "options": ["Han Meimei passed the exam after playing the games.", "Li Hua leant many English words from playing games.", "Sunyan worked well with his teammates", "Yang Li let out his anger and expressions."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2180, "question": "The owner of an Alabama Chinese restaurant named \"Good Friend\" shot at a customer who complained about a fly in her eggroll Thursday night. The bullet narrowly missed 20-year-old Birmingham resident Jatari Walker who told the Daily News she is scarred by the entire experience. \"I can't sleep,\" she said Saturday afternoon. \"And since it happened I've had no appetite.\" Walker ordered a combination platter and eggroll from the Good Friend Chinese and Seafood Restaurant on Dennison Ave. Thursday evening. After paying her $7 bill she went back to her car and discovered a fly inside. \"I thought I need to take this back,\" she said. The customer went back and asked for a repayment and said the owner Chun HinChing, 52, was unhappy with her because she announced her discovery in front of other custo...\n\nQ: What happened on Thursday night in Good Friend Chinese and Seafood Restaurant?", "options": ["A fire broke out but luckily no one was injured.", "The restaurant owner refused to repay the money.", "The egg rolls caused sickness among some customers.", "A young woman narrowly escaped being killed by a bullet."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2042, "question": "I arrived at the bus station much too early for the London bus, which was not to leave until five to twelve. I pushed through the crowds, looking for somewhere to sit down. Scores of people were standing about, or struggling along with their bags and the cases to find the right lines. There was a party of school girls. I could see teachers trying to keep them in order. But there was nowhere for me to sit. I stepped into the station buffet. I looked up at the clock there. It was only twenty to twelve. I found a seat opposite a large mirror on the wall. Just then a friend of mine called Jim came in and sat with me. \"What time is your bus?\" asked Jim. \"Oh, there's a plenty of time yet,\" I answered. \"Oh, I'll get some drinks then,\" said Jim. We talked while drinking. Then I looked at the clock...\n\nQ: The writer sat   _  .", "options": ["behind a mirror", "facing a mirror", "under a mirror", "near a mirror"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1106, "question": "\"Family\" is of course an _ word. But when British people say that their society is based on family life, they are thinking of \"family\" in its narrow, peculiarly European sense of mother ,father and children living together alone in their own house as an economic and social unit. Thus, every British marriage indicates the beginning of a new and independent family--hence the tremendous importance of marriage in British life. For both the man and the woman, marriage means leaving one's parents and starting one's own life. The man's first duty will then be to his wife, and the wife's to her husband. He will be entirely responsible for her financial support, and she for the running of the new home. Their children will be their common responsibility and theirs alone. Neither the wife's parents n...\n\nQ: What is true concerning the book Pride and Prejudice?", "options": ["It is the best book on marriage.", "It is a handbook of marriage.", "It gives quite some idea of English social life in the past.", "It provides a lot of information of former time wealthy families."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 862, "question": "Nathan's second-hand bike was good enough to get him anywhere he wanted to go. Of course, it couldn't match Tim's in a normal speed race, but all the fancy gears in the world wouldn't get you up Black Mountain. It was so steep in places that you had to get off your bike and push. On this particular afternoon, the odds were all on Nathan's side. First, he was stronger. Tim had always been thin, but recently he'd started to grow so fast that his arms and legs were like pieces of spaghetti. As well as being considerably fitter than his friend, Nathan knew the shortcuts up prefix = st1 /BlackMountain. So when Nathan accepted the challenge, he was sure he'd win. He nearly always did, in competitions with Tim. That was what was strange. Tim was so competitive, and yet he wasn't any good at physi...\n\nQ: Which of the following advantages did Nathan have over Tim?", "options": ["Nathan had a better bike and knew the shortcuts up the mountain.", "Nathan was fitter and knew the quickest ways up the mountain.", "Nathan was stronger and more competitive than Tim.", "Nathan was stronger and had a better bike."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1346, "question": "Six seconds after its launch in Virginia, US, an unmanned rocket bound for the International Space Station (ISS) exploded, disappointing people both on Earth and in space. Hundreds of millions of dollars worth of cargo was destroyed in the Oct. 28 explosion due to An\"equipment failure\", said Orbital Sciences, the company hired by NASA for the resupply mission. The rocket was carrying a cargo ship loaded with 2,200 kilograms of supplies such as food, tools, parts, and experiments. Roughly a third of the cargo was a series of scientific investigations. Some of them were from high school students in the US. For example, 10 students from the Cristo Rey Jesuit College Preparatory School of Houston were conducting experiments about microgravity and put their samples on the rocket. \"I know that f...\n\nQ: What is the author-s main purpose in writing the article?", "options": ["To explain what caused the explosion of NASA-s unmanned rocket.", "To inform us of the explosion of NASA-s unmanned rocket and its effects.", "To tell us about astronauts lives at the International Space Station.", "To tell us how the world reacted to the explosion of NASA-s unmanned rocket."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 880, "question": "If you're in charge of a project, the key to success is getting everyone to want to help you. As a director, I point, I suggest, I gently push the actors in the direction I want them to go. In the 1986 movie Nothing in Common, Jackie Gleason's character, Max Basner, gets fired (or unemployed) from his job as a clothing salesman. The scene, shot on a boat, shows Max's despair about being out of work. I was looking for some gesture that would allow Max to show his feelings. Jackie had far more experience at everything than I did, and at first I was frightened (very much afraid). What could I possibly tell \"The Great One\" about acting? Out of fear I decided to direct by suggestion, and I sat down with Gleason to talk about the scene. \"So Max is sad, right?\" I said. Gleason nodded. \"And he's p...\n\nQ: The author tells us that to succeed in a project you are in charge of, you should   _  .", "options": ["make everyone work for you", "get everyone willing to help you", "let people know you have the final say", "keep sending out orders to them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1404, "question": "China's former volleyball star Lang Ping has been invited to coach the US women's national team for the Beijing 2008 Olympics. But China's sports media said the offer would be difficult to accept. Lang, who is presently coaching a club team in Italy's professional volleyball league, told sina.com that she was considering the offer by the US Volleyball Association. \"Right now I'm still considering their offer but I will answer them soon,\"Lang said. \"If I don't take the job, I have to give them enough time to find someone else.\" Lang, 45,won Olympic gold in 1984. She later coached the Chinese women to silver at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics and the 1998 World Championships. She has also coached at New Mexico University in the United States where her daughter was born and lives. The reaction in t...\n\nQ: According to the text, if Lang Ping stands with the opponents during women's volleyball matches, who will most probably have trouble?", "options": ["The Chinese audience.", "Our women's volleyball team.", "Beijing 2008 Olympics.", "Chinese former players."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 140, "question": "Dear Earthmen , I have enjoyed my stay on your interesting unusual planet. I think I understand the life on earth now and I would like to give you my impressions. First of all you live in boxes. Every morning you leave your big boxes and get into smaller boxes on wheels. All these small boxes race around and around, and finally stop to rest. You then leave these boxes on wheels and go to very large tall boxes. After testing all days you get back in your little boxes and return to your big boxes. There you sit and stare at tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front. Only one thing puzzles me. One day I went to a football game. A bunch of angry boys fought over a little round ball. Everyone yelled for them to stop but they kept on fighting. They were angry, I suppose, about being c...\n\nQ: The man from the Mars thinks  _  .", "options": ["it interesting to experience a lot on our unusual planet", "there are so many boxes on the earth", "the tiny glowing boxes are moving pictures", "the angry boys are too foolish to fight over a little round ball"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1888, "question": "A brother and sister have been reunited after more than 60 years, thanks to a letter in the Welwyn and Hatfield Times. For years John Hannant Kept a photograph of his long-lost sister, hoping they would meet again. Margery, the eldest of the three children, had signed up to the Royal Air Force as part of the war effort, when John was still a baby. The family lost touch and as the decade s passed only a single letter gave a clue to her whereabouts. The clue was enough for a WHT reader to recognize Margery and put the family back in touch.. John, 67, had been searching for a long time and a friend suggested writing to the paper. \"That's the one that made it, the letter to the paper a few months age,\" he said. \"It's like a dream come true. The last time we ever heard from Margery was in 1953 ...\n\nQ: When she wrote to John last time ,Margery was   _", "options": ["34 years old", "40 years old", "44years old", "54 years old"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3314, "question": "There has been much discussion recently about reducing the weight of English in China's high-stake tests such as the national college entrance examination. It is argued by some applauding the recent change to reduce the importance of English in tests so that it will lead students to focus more on learning Chinese. The TV program Writing in Chinese has exposed the problem that students and the general public cannot write in Chinese as they used to do. Some blame the design of the curriculum for giving English an equal or greater amount of emphasis, which might have contributed to the failure in teaching Chinese. But this is probably not a fair accusation since children in English speaking countries cannot spell either. I doubt that studying English in itself hurts the study of Chinese. In f...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best serve as the title of the passage?", "options": ["English education is still important in China.", "Chinese education is more important in China.", "English contributes to the failure in teaching Chinese", "Ways to make improvements in learning Chinese."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2242, "question": "Supermarket Morrisons today announced to launch an online shopping operation within two years in a move to catch up with its web-savvy rivals. The UK's fourth biggest supermarket said Morrisons.com would offer grocery and non-food products but would take time to build from zero. As part of its online development, Morrisons - the only one of the \"Big Four\" grocers to have a significant internet business - revealed it had invested PS32 million in a 10% stake of a New York-based online grocer. The announcement came as Morrisons posted a 13% increase in underlying pre-tax profits of PS869 million in the year to January 30. Morrisons is implementing a growth strategy which is focused on expanding its e-commerce business and moving into the convenience store market. It has earmarked PS3 billion ...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Morrisons Has Many Business Rvials", "Morrisons Will Launch an Online Operation", "Morrisons Switches to Run Online Shopping", "Morrisons Wants to Establish Branches"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1154, "question": "Some nations think they must have more and more babies, more and more people, if they are to remain strong and free. Actually, this is not so. Very often in history, small nations have conquered large ones. It's not so much the size of the army as its organization and the technical level of its weapons. Thus, Greece took over Persia in the 300s B.C., Great Britain took over India in the 1700s, even though Persia and India had far bigger population than Greece and Great Britain. If a nation wishes to avoid being dominated by its neighbors, its best chance is to raise its standard of living and its level of technology. _ can be done best by not allowing its population to grow to such a point that it is sunk in misery and poverty. In fact, the worst way in which a nation can try to avoid bein...\n\nQ: What might the author be further discussing after the passage?", "options": ["Needs to balance population.", "Problems involved in birth control.", "Methods of decreasing population.", "Opposition from some nations."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 966, "question": "The skin which covers the tips of the fingers and thumbs is crossed by numerous ridges arranged in different patterns. These patterns are permanent from birth and remain exactly the same throughout a person's life, even when the skin becomes wrinkled and cracked as a result of old age. Such patterns are never passed on from parents to children, and no one in the world has the same patterns as anyone else. Even identical twins have different sets of fingerprints. As a result, fingerprints offer a most useful and _ way of identifying people. Any ridged part of the hand and the foot may be used as a means of identification, but finger impressions are usually preferred since they can be taken easily and quickly. Fingerprints are classified in the ways: by general shapes and contours , by the f...\n\nQ: We prefer to use fingerprints to identify people because   _  .", "options": ["we can never find the same set of fingerprints among human beings", "finger impressions can be taken easily and quickly", "fingerprints offer a most useful and foolproof way of identifying people", "all of the above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 781, "question": "The Pew report,which was based on surveys carried out in Britain,France,Germany, Italy,Spain,Greece, Poland and the Czech Republic,said that the European Union was \"the new sick man of Europe\".The percentage of Europeans with a good view of the EU has fallen from 60 percent last year to 45 percent now. The UK may be considered the most Eurosceptic country ,but its support for the Union has barely changed in the past 1 2 months,falling only two points to 43 percent.But,France's backing for the EU has fallen sharply,from 60 percent last year to 41 percent today. On the question of whether to remain in the EU, 46 percent of the British want to leave the Union and surprisingly,the same percentage want to stay. The Pew report's authors said, \"The long-term economic crisis has created bad forces...\n\nQ: Prime Minister David Cameron feels a little bit comfortable for   _   .", "options": ["only a score of 37 percent of the Britons go against him", "many of the Polish and the French think highly of him", "more than 60 percent of the voters are in favor of keeping the EU", "Angela Merkel has 74 percent of the voters"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2256, "question": "To me, the ocean is our greatest wilderness. I love swimming in it , surfing its waves, watching it from shore and thinking about all the life living unseen under the surface. When I take my little kids to check out tide pools, we're overjoyed when we find a sea star or some shellfish. Lately, though, I've noticed a change in my favorite pools: there are more sea grasses and fewer animals with shells. I can't help feeling these small changes _ something more troubling about our oceans. It matches what scientists are telling us: our oceans are being troubled by carbon dioxide that threatens corals, colorful fish, salmon, sea otters, even whales. Our oceans are facing a major change. Every hour, a million tons of carbon dioxide from cars, factories and power plants rain down on the world's o...\n\nQ: The author's recent visits to the tide pool brought her   _   .", "options": ["happiness", "anger", "concern", "comfort"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 5, "question": "There is probably no field of human activity in which our values and lifestyles are shown more clearly and strongly than they are in the clothes that we choose to wear.The dress of an individual is a kind of \"sign language\" that communicates a set of information and is usually the basis on which immediate impressions are formed.Traditionally,a concern for clothes was considered to be an affair of females,while men took pride in the fact that they were completely lacking in clothes consciousness . This type of American culture is by degrees changing as man dress takes on greater variety and color.Even as early as 1955,a researcher in Michigan said that _ White collar workers in particular viewed dress as a symbol of ability,which could be used to impress or influence others,especially in th...\n\nQ: Blue collar workers pay attention to their clothes because   _  .", "options": ["they are concerned about the impression their clothes make on their superiors", "they know very clearly that people will judge them on the basis of their clothing", "they want to impress and influence others", "they don't want to be laughed at"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 767, "question": "As shocking as the idea of baby birds growing up in a cigarette-filled home sounds, a new study suggests that some birds may benefit from putting the stuff from cigarette butts into their nests. The nicotine remaining in smoked filters may serve as a natural insecticide , driving harmful insects away from the nests and the baby birds living within. Tobacco plants produce nicotine because it defends against insects that would otherwise eat the plants. The butts are undoubtedly smelly. But birds are actually quite fond of smelly chemicals, such as those found in aromatic plants. Some nest-building species regularly fill their nests with fresh aromatics, possibly because the chemicals are good for the immune system or the development of the chicks. Alternatively, the plant chemicals might act...\n\nQ: What may be the function of nicotine in cigarette butts for birds?", "options": ["To provide building materials for bird nests.", "To drive harmful insects away from bird nests.", "To protect the plants from being eaten by insects.", "To attract baby birds to stay in the nests."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 172, "question": "China has recently been faced with serious issues of product safety. In Panama, it is said that medicine made with a poisonous chemical sickened some people. A Chinese company had identified it as diethylamide glycol ( []), a low - cost substitute commonly used in automobile antifreeze . Some countries have banned Chinese-made toothpaste containing diethylamide glycol. China has now told companies to discontinue its use, even though it says the toothpaste is safe. Another industrial chemical, melamine, was found in wheat flour used to make pet food in North America. Thousands of dogs and cats became sick. The United States has restricted some imports of Chinese seafood because they contained banned substance. And questions have been raised about other products, including children's toys co...\n\nQ: We can infer the followings except that   _  .", "options": ["Chinese- made toothpaste is safe", "the safety of \"made in China\" is doubted", "there are safety problems with more Chinese products", "the Chinese government is to blame partly for the product safety problems."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1650, "question": "Think of London and you're likely to think of the city's famous bright red double-deckers buses. Think of Thailand's capital city, Bangkok, and the noisy tuk-tuk ( ) may come to mind. Picture the American city of San Francisco and you might see the city's trolleybuses. Imagining what these cities would look like without their red buses, tuk-tuks or trolleybuses is difficult. They are symbols of these cities that make them different from anywhere else in the world. However, these city symbols, which are so loved by tourists, are not always so well loved by their city leaders. City leaders want what is best for their city, which often means the most modern transport. In Thailand, Bangkok city authorities have forbidden new tuk-tuks because they consider them noisy and polluting. However, the...\n\nQ: The London double-decker bus is returning mainly because   _  .", "options": ["it is an improved version", "the new mayor also loves it", "it is popular with tourists", "Londoners fought for it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 152, "question": "As the train approached the seaside town where I was going to spend my holiday, I went into the corridor to stretch my legs.I stayed there for a short while,breathing in the fresh air and exchanging a few words with one of the passengers,whom I had met earlier on the station platform. When I turned to go back to my seat,I happened to glance into the compartment next to mine.Sitting there was a man who many years before had been my neighbor.He was a great talker, I remembered;it used to take hours to get away from him once he began talking.I was not at all sorry when he went to live in another part of London.We had not met since then,nor did I wish to meet him now, when my holiday was about to begin. Luckily at that moment he was much too busy talking to the man opposite him to have the cha...\n\nQ: \"in no time\" means_.", "options": ["having no time", "very quickly", "in the near future", "sooner or later"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 314, "question": "In today's Internet age, online games can be a change from the pressure of school and work. However, they can also cause problems and unhealthy addictions. This is most clearly seen in the example of South Korea. This country has the world's highest percentage of high-speed Internet services. It also has a high number of game players who are addicted to online games. In 2004, a young man died after playing online games almost nonstop for 86 hours. A 12-year-old boy stole $16,000 from his father to continue online games which he could not get away from. Such problems are spreading to other parts of Asia as well. In 2005, it was reported that about 80 percent of China's 13.8 million online game players were under 25. And many of these were said to be addicted. Such numbers point toward a gro...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["reasons for online game addiction", "problems caused by online games", "computer problems in Asia", "problems caused by young people"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1960, "question": "Every year, Americans send millions of tons of food to the landfill . What if you could use all of those rotten vegetables to heat your home? That's happening in one unlikely laboratory: the Newtown Creek Wastewater Treatment Plan in Brooklyn The plant's longtime manager, Jimmy Pynn, shows off the plant's crown jewels: eight huge, shiny, oval-shaped steel tanks known as digester eggs. Each one contains millions of gallons of black material that's roughly pea soup. Pynn calls it \"black gold\". \"The digesters like to be fed like us: three times a day,\" he says. \"They like to be kept warm, 98 degrees. And that's what we have these guys for: to make methane ,which can be used to heat homes or make electricity.\" Right now, what these bacteria are digesting is mostly sewage mud. But they are bein...\n\nQ: What role are the digester eggs expected to play?", "options": ["To get black gold from daily waste.", "To produce new diet for humans.", "To change food scraps into gas.", "To make crown jewels."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2538, "question": "When you sleep somewhere else--like at summer camp or a friend's house--you know you're in for a fun time. It can be exciting to get away from the same old bed in the same old room in the same old house. But fun as this is, for some kids being away from home can be scary and sad. They want to go and have fun with their friends, but once they're there, they start to miss their good old bed, their good old parents, and all that everyday stuff at home. It's called being homesick. Homesick means you're upset, sad, and maybe scared. But don't feel surprised. A lot of people get homesick, even grownups. When you're used to having certain people and things around you, it can be scary when they're gone. When you're dealing with other problems, you will feel homesick, too. Some kids may feel more h...\n\nQ: There are   _   ideas to help you feel less homesick mentioned in this passage.", "options": ["five", "four", "three", "Two"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1629, "question": "Is it possible to persuade mankind to live without war? War is an ancient institution,-which has existed for at least six thousand years.It was always bad and usually foolish, but in the past human race managed to live with it.Modern inventiveness has changed this.Either man will end war, or war will end man.For the present, it is nuclear weapons that cause the most serious danger, but bacteriological or chemical weapons may, before Iong, offer an even greater threat.If we succeed in ending nuclear weapons, our work will not be done.It will never be done until we have succeeded in ending war.To do _ , we need to persuade mankind to look upon international questions in a new way, not as contests of force, in which the victory goes to the side which is most skillful in kiting people, but by ...\n\nQ: In the sentence \"To do this, we need to persuade mankind\" (Para l), \"this\" refers to  _", "options": ["abolish war", "improve weapons", "solve international problems", "live a peaceful life"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2197, "question": "Medicine comes in lots of different packages. Painkillers in a tablet can make your headache go away. Antibiotic cream from a tube can prevent your cuts from becoming infected. But can medicine come packaged in chicken eggs? A team of scientists from Scotland say \"yes\". They've engineered special chickens that lay eggs with disease-treating drugs inside. These eggs come from chickens that have been engineered to produce certain drugs inside their egg whites. These drugs are made of molecules called proteins . Animals make thousands of proteins -- they're the main element in skin, hair, milk and meat. Since animals can make proteins easily, they're good candidates for making protein drugs. Researchers have already made cows, sheep and goats produce protein drugs in their milk. But chickens ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["Scientists from Scotland have succeeded in packing medicine into chicken eggs.", "The drugs are made of molecules called proteins.", "Scientists chose chickens for their experiments because chicken eggs taste delicious.", "The animals are good candidates for making protein drugs."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2783, "question": "Elephants scored a big win in Dohar, Qatar, on March 22, 2010. Representatives from 175 countries met in the Middle Eastem country. They voted to continue a ban on the sale of ivory . Two African nations, Tanzania and Zambia, had asked to open up the ivory trade. People feared that weakening a 21-year-old ban on the sale of ivory would encourage illegal hunting and hurt elephant populations. African elephants once numbered in the millions. Today, there are fewer than 500,000. \"People born in 100 years should be able to see an elephant,\" said Noah Wekesa, Kenya's minister of forest and wildlife. His country voted to keep the ban. In the 1980s, as many as 1 million elephants were killed throughout Africa. Hunters killed the animals for their ivory tusks, which were used to make jewelry and o...\n\nQ: Tanzania and Zambia asked for permission to   _  .", "options": ["Sell elephants", "sell jewelry made from ivory", "sell their stocked ivory", "continue hunting for ivory"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 894, "question": "Do you want to write your password down so that no one can see it, or do you want to send someone a secret message? Knowing how to make an invisible ink message will have you feeling like a secret agent in no time. These are instructions for making invisible ink using baking soda. Difficulty: Easy Time required: A few minutes What you need: Baking soda, Paper, Water, Light bulb, Paintbrush, Measuring cup, Purple grape juice Here's how: There are at least two methods of using baking soda as invisible ink. Mix equal amounts of water and baking soda. Use a paintbrush to write a message onto white paper, using the baking soda solution as \"ink\". Allow the ink to dry. One way to read the message is to hold the paper up to a heat source, such as a light bulb. The baking soda will cause the writin...\n\nQ: is not needed for making invisible ink.", "options": ["Baking soda", "Paper", "Water", "Ink"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3116, "question": "Lindsay Morgan Lohan was born on July 2, 1986. She was such a natural beauty that she began modeling at the age of 3, and because of her natural talent, she played parts in over 60 TV commercials for companies such as Abercrombie & Fitch, Wendy's, the Gap, Pizza Hut, Calvin Klein, and Jell-O, in which she shared the screen with Bill Cosby. When she was 7, Lohan was required to dress up as garbage for a Halloween short play on the Late Show with David Letterman called \"Things You Find on the Bottom of the Subway.\" It was her first real acting job. In 1996, Lohan got her second big _ when she was given a role on the long-running NBC soap opera \"Another World.\" For only one season, she became the third actress to act the part Alexandra Alli Fowler. Shortly after, she hit the highway to fame w...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Lohan has played three films produced by Disney.", "Lohan played the part Bill Cosby in a TV show.", "Lohan has released two albums since 2005.", "Lohan was greatly influenced by Emilio Estefan Jr."], "answer": 2}]